Sagarika Sant (1) Featured

System Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Hadoop, Core Java, Android, MySQL, Unix, Bash, Groovy, Python, Powershell Scripting



Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 8 Month(s) Current Designation: System Engineer -Core Java

Current Company: Tata Consultancy Services Notice Period: 3 Months Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: BE [CS]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: System Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, Hadoop, Core

Java, Android, MySQL, Unix, Bash, Groovy, Python, Powershell Scripting

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Working as a Solution Architect in "digitate" from Jan 2019- Now Trained in RPA technology and working on ignio (RPA tool) developed by Tata consultancy service.

Got appreciation for the work done in implementation of use cases(robots) in ignio production environment.

Have experience in requirement gathering, design document

building, unit testing, UAT and post Go-live support. Have an extensive skill in communication, excellent team player,

debugging skills and client interaction.

Have successfully completed 2 projects of ignio implementation in 2 different accounts from requirement gathering to development of use case and post implementation support.

Worked on development and customization of usecases as per business requirements.

Have 1 year of technical experience in splunk, servicenow, solarwinds and various CRM applications like ACT, Gorilla, Goldmine, BrokersAlly.

Work Experience

Tata Consultancy Services as System Engineer -Core Java Mar 2018 to Till Date

Project: Ignio Implementation January 2020- Present

Account: Digitate Team: Product Specialist

Project Roles and Responsibilities:

Our project undergoes implementation of the ignio(RPA tool) a Tata

consultancy service product, in our client's environment.

The ignio implementation is performed in an agile manner which is classified in sprints. The sprint involves: Requirement gathering from client, developing a foundation architecture of the processes, analyzing the usecases, development and customization, installation of ignio in pre production environment, Usecase Integration in ignio pre prod, Usecase execution and testing, production installation, Adapter and usecase Integration with production environment, Healthcheck configuration, Production testing, post implementation support.

Our role is to gather requirements from clients, developing and customizing usecases, ignio installation and integration, healthcheck configuration, design documents/report creation and testing.

Tools and Platforms used: Windows Powershell, Linux, Digitate studio, confluence, Ignio environment, ServiceNow, Solarwinds

Project: Global Wealth Management July 2018- Dec 2019

Account: Morgan Stanley

Team: Application Engineering and Integration Services

Project Roles and Responsibilities:

The role was to deal with the application onboarding and packaging for our client users.

Handled end to end data migration of our wealth management clients during windows migration.

Handled end to end CRM application technicalities and specification including the databases.

Worked as an L3 support team for CRM and database on ServiceNow.

Developed scripts and tools in windows powershell in order to automate the process.

Tools and Platforms used: Windows Powershell, Powershell Studio, ACT, BrokersAlly, Gorilla, Goldmine, Splunk, Sql server management studio, Jira, Jive, Service Now, Blastmail, Global Management Console, TAI.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2017

PG: BE (CS) from Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya (RGPV), Bhopal in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
HADOOP			
CORE JAVA			
ANDROID			
MySQL			
Unix			
BASH			
GROOVY			
Python			
PowerShell Scripting			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	

1/22/2021		https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=1b90ab329bc28ab3540fc8148d0697055e0901534e150a420217125f54		
	English			
	Hindi			
	Marathi			

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time